quiz = {
    1 : {
        "question" : "1.What is the room in the Engineering Building entrance called (where the concrete canoe is placed",
        "answer" : "The Atrium"
    },
    2 : {
        "question" : "2.How many floors are there in the Engineering Building and the SICCS building, combined?",
        "answer" : "6"
    },
    3 : {
        "question" : "3.What time do the computers in the computer labs in the Engineering building restart? ",
        "answer" : "12 am"
    },
    4 : {
        "question" : "4.How do you check out a calculator from the front desk?",
        "answer" : "Leave your ID at the front desk"
    },
    5 : {
        "question" : "5.True or False: There are 4 entrances into the Engineering building?",
        "answer" : "false"
    },
    6 : {
        "question" : "What year did CEFNS and CEIAS split?",
        "answer" : "2018"
    },
    7 : {
        "question" : "How many student clubs and organizations are affiliated with CEIAS?",
        "answer" : "26"
    },
    8 : {
        "question" : "What is the name of the Dean of CEIAS?",
        "answer" : "Andy Wang"
    },
    9 : {
        "question" : "What is the name of the center within APMS?",
        "answer" : "MIRA"
    },
    10 : {
        "question" : "What year did CEFNS and CEIAS split?",
        "answer" : "2018"
    },
    11 : {
        "question" : "How many PhD programs are offered through CEIAS? ",
        "answer" : "4"
    },
    12 : {
        "question" : "How many full-time faculty does CEIAS have for Spring 21?",
        "answer" : "97"
    }
}